[{"answer": "Since we're pretty familiar in the community, several people in the community started texting us about, oh, 9:00 that morning, and, you know, of course, there are no secrets in a small town.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "How do you guys find out about this, Walt?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "It really is a wonderful pre-holiday story, isn't it?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "All they said today was that they were definitely going to take care of their family and their grandchildren and set up college funds for them, and then they had some charities they are really into the adoption and so I know that they were possibly thinking about getting another child, and making sure that the adoption community, you know, gets some of their money.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Have they given any indication to you?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "We did.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Walt, did you buy tickets yourselves for this Powerball?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "He's not going back to work.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "What's going to happen to Mark's job now with all this?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Well, I knew that it was going to be a difficult challenge and so the first thing I tried to do was put together a great coaching staff and I think that's what we've done here.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "When you took over from the legendary Joe Paterno with all the shame and scandal that had befallen Penn State -- be honest with me, what was really going through your mind?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Well, I believe that we have great communication with our players, number one.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "How have you reassured everybody that there's a whole new world now at Penn State and they don't have to worry about it?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'll start with Coach Paterno.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "And what are your thoughts personally towards Joe Paterno and indeed, towards Jerry Sandusky?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "I love you more, by the way, and I'm fine.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Five years.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Was it really?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "You do look great, I have got to say.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "We had a blast, didn't we?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "I couldn't see myself going through chemo again.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "How did you feel when you got this back and thought, here we go again?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Relieved.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "How did you feel?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "No, because I never -- I never believe those surveys, anyway, because they're always wrong.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Is that what went through your mind, that even if there's one percent chance, you don't want to take it?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "You know, I think my mom and dad took the news far worse than I did.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "How have your mom and dad been?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Pathetic.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "You never stop booing the whole time, did you?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "She's trying to bite him.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "He's not trying to bite the baby, is he?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "-- clearly missing me, you clearly missing me.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "I do not know.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "What went wrong?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I thought he handled himself really well, because we know him as the Howard Stern of radio.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Did you feel that?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "They did offer Jack the job.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "What was the truth?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "I watch them all.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Do you like any of them?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Oh, dear.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Who is the worst judge on television at the moment?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I would love you to come back.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Am I allowed back soon?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Next week.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "When are you in New York next?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Do you know what, I just had my tea.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Would you like another picture?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Well, actually, you know, having this plane crash in the movie was a detriment to my possible decision, because I had done a plane crash in \"Castaway\" with Tom Hanks.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Was it that -- was it the concept of being able to create this incredible scene that really attracted you to the movie?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "You need an actor of his kind of brilliance, don't you?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Does he deserve an Oscar, do you think?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think about it that often.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "Do you ever stop and think about that?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Thirty one million, yes.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "It was about 30 million?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well, about 77, 78 million.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "And it's grossed what so far?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "For me, my -- I have done this my entire career.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "How do you quantify in the modern game of movies a real success?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- well, I've worked with a lot of great actors, I mean magnificent actors.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "What does it take to be really top draw?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121130pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Is that your reading of it?", "qSentId": 622}]